var random = Math.floor(Math.random() * 6);

if(random == 0){
  var quiz =[
    { question:'散歩', answer:'さんぽ'},
    { question:'静脈', answer:'じょうみゃく'},
    { question:'厄介', answer:'やっかい'},
    { question:'容赦', answer:'ようしゃ'},
    { question:'盤石', answer:'ばんじゃく'},
    { question:'浄瑠璃', answer:'じょうるり'},
    { question:'踵', answer:'かかと'},
    { question:'夥<span>しい</span>', answer:'おびただ'},
    { question:'殊更', answer:'ことさら'},
    { question:'草臥<span>れる</span>', answer:'くたび'}
   ];
}else if(random == 1){
  var quiz =[
  { question:'真珠', answer:'しんじゅ'},
  { question:'獲物', answer:'えもの'},
  { question:'暴露', answer:'ばくろ'},
  { question:'幸先', answer:'さいさき'},
  { question:'名残', answer:'なごり'},
  { question:'培<span>う</span>', answer:'つちか'},
  { question:'怠<span>い</span>', answer:'だる'},
  { question:'仄<span>か</span>', answer:'ほの'},
  { question:'擽<span>る</span>', answer:'くすぐ'},
  { question:'譫言', answer:'うわごと'}
 ];
}else if(random == 2){
  var quiz =[
  { question:'記述', answer:'きじゅつ'},
  { question:'強引', answer:'ごういん'},
  { question:'暴露', answer:'ばくろ'},
  { question:'矛盾', answer:'むじゅん'},
  { question:'閲覧', answer:'えつらん'},
  { question:'暫定', answer:'ざんてい'},
  { question:'潰<span>える</span>', answer:'つい'},
  { question:'邁進', answer:'まいしん'},
  { question:'伝播<span>する</span>', answer:'でんぱ'},
  { question:'屯<span>する</span>', answer:'たむろ'}
 ];
}else if(random == 3){
  var quiz =[
  { question:'自然', answer:'しぜん'},
  { question:'稽古', answer:'けいこ'},
  { question:'滑走', answer:'かっそう'},
  { question:'慰<span>める</span>', answer:'なぐさ'},
  { question:'贋作', answer:'がんさく'},
  { question:'掴<span>む</span>', answer:'つか'},
  { question:'揶揄', answer:'やゆ'},
  { question:'頸椎', answer:'けいつい'},
  { question:'長閑', answer:'のどか'},
  { question:'燥<span>ぐ</span>', answer:'はしゃ'}
 ];
}else if(random == 4){
  var quiz =[
  { question:'鉄棒', answer:'てつぼう'},
  { question:'合併', answer:'がっぺい'},
  { question:'溶岩', answer:'ようがん'},
  { question:'抱負', answer:'ほうふ'},
  { question:'聴取', answer:'ちょうしゅ'},
  { question:'侘<span>しい</span>', answer:'わび'},
  { question:'奉<span>る</span>', answer:'たてまつ'},
  { question:'気儘', answer:'きまま'},
  { question:'鯉幟', answer:'こいのぼり'},
  { question:'甚振<span>る</span>', answer:'いたぶ'}
 ];
}else{
  var quiz =[
  { question:'見栄', answer:'みえ'},
  { question:'応<span>える</span>', answer:'こた'},
  { question:'解毒', answer:'げどく'},
  { question:'傘下', answer:'さんか'},
  { question:'履修', answer:'りしゅう'},
  { question:'片鱗', answer:'へんりん'},
  { question:'俄<span>かに</span>', answer:'にわ'},
  { question:'若布', answer:'わかめ'},
  { question:'過<span>る</span>', answer:'よぎ'},
  { question:'軈<span>て</span>', answer:'やが'}
 ];
}
